1	"Event [%s] has finished"
2	"New Event [%s] has started"
3	"- Kill [%d] [%s]"
4	"- Kill [%d] players in [%s]"
5	"- Kill [%d] player in any of the following maps:"
6	"- Kill [%d] [%s] in [%s]"
7	"- Kill [%d] [%s] in any of the following maps:"
8	"- Find [%d] [%s] hidden in in any of the following maps:"
9	"Found"
10	"Killed"
11	"Players Killed"
12	"End Date"
13	"Active Events"
14	"You are unable to kill an Event Mob."
15	"You are unable to pick up an Event Item."
16	"Mob is already getting attacked by another player"
17	"Event started Successfully"
18	"Event Abadoned Successfully"
19	"Ends in: %d days, %d hours, %d minutes"
20	"Event [%s] Successfully completed"
21	"Failed to give Event Reward. Your Inventory is full. You need about %d free slots to claim the event rewards"
22	"Start"
23	"Leave"
24	"Claim Rewards"
25	"Do you really want to Start the event?"
26	"You have already started this event"
27	"Do you really want to Leave the event?"
28	"You haven't started this event"
29	"Do you really want to claim the rewards?"
30	"%s Event Completed. Claim your rewards from the event window"
31	"Event failed to start. The Minimum level requirement for this event is %d"
32	"This is a character bound event. Another character of yours already started this event"
33	"%s"
34	"You have to select an event"
35	"This is an event Item, it can't be picked up"
36	"(%d day(s))"
37	"(%d hour(s))"
38	"(%d minute(s))"
39	"You haven't completed that event"
40	"You have reached the maximum number of times you can participate in this event."
41	"- Kill [%d] player(s)"
42	"- Kill [%d] [%s]"
43	"- Find [%d] [%s]. Can be hidden on any map"
44	"(Ends in: %d second(s))"
45	"Error Occurred whilst trying to start event"
46	"Error Occurred whilst trying to leave event"
47	"(Lv%d - Lv%d)"
48	"You need the (%s) to enter this map"
49	"The (%s) has expired"
50	"Event failed to start. The Maximum level requirement for this event is %d"
51	"Token(s) Total"
52	"Copper"
53	"Silver"
54	"Gold"
55	"Obsidian"
56	"Normal"
57	"Prev"
58	"Next"
59	"Buy"
60	"Reset"
61	"Exchange Tokens"
62	"Exchange Details"
63	"Current Total:"
64	"Price:"
65	"Total:"
66	"You do not have enough %s to complete the token exchange"
67	"You have successfully exchanged %d %s to %d %s."
68	"A vendor shop is currently opened. Please close this and try again."
69	"Your level is too low to use this store. Min level is: %d."
70	"Your level is too high to use this store. Max level is: %d."
71 	"Vendor is currently not active at this times."
72	"You do not have enough tokens to buy all the items."
73	"Something went wrong during pruchase. Please try again!"
74	"Token Set successfully!"
75	"Tokens"
76	"Token Exchange"
77	"Exchange"
78	"Ascending"
79	"Descending"
80	"Filter"
81	"Tokens"
82	"You can only purchase %d %s."
83	""